A Guide to the Campbell Brown Collection, 1793-1886
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Collection, 1793-1886
Library of Virginia
20799
1 volume (274 leaves)
Campbell Brown
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Lent for copying by Percy Brown, Charlottesville, Virginia, 10 February 1931, 12 February 1931, and 19 October 1934.
Biographical/Historical Information
Campbell Brown was born on 27 November 1840 to Percy and Lizinka Brown. He was the cousin, stepson, and staff officer of Confederate General Richard S. Ewell during the Civil War. Ewell married Lizinka, his first cousin, in 1862. Brown was the grandson of George Washington Campbell Brown and the nephew of David Hubbard. He committed suicide on 30 August 1893.
Scope and Content Information
Collection of papers of George Washington Campbell (1769-1848) and his sons-in-law, David Hubbard (ca. 1792-1874) and Richard Stoddert Ewell (1817-1872).
The George Washington Campbell Papers cover the years 1793-1833, and include 115 items. Principal correspondents are John Jacob Astor, H.A.S. Dearborn, David Hubbard, Andrew Jackson, Thomas Jefferson, James Madison, James Monroe, and Richard Rush. Topics covered include Campbell's health and personal and business affairs, state and national political appointments and elections, Aaron Burr, the Mississippi Territory, Indian affairs, notably relations with the Creek and Chicasaw tribes, French politics, ceding of Florida lands by Spain, the War of 1812, including the fall of Washington, D.C., and Campbell's and John Armstrong's role in it. There are also copies of Campbell's resignation letter as Secretary of the Treasury and President Madison's acceptance, President Monroe's letter offering Campbell the appointment as Minister to Russia, and various letters from individuals wishing him success in that post and offering him assistance.
The David Hubbard Papers cover the years 1834-1861, and include 17 items. Principal correspondents are John C. Calhoun, D.H. Lewis, and James K. Polk. Topics covered include national political issues and legislation, Nicholas Biddle and the Bank of the United States, the election of Polk as President, as well as issues concerning various national political conventions and party politics in general. There is also a map of the battleground of Manassas (1861).
The Richard Stoddert Ewell Papers cover the years 1862 to 1885, and include 16 items. Principal correspondents include Jefferson Davis and Robert E. Lee. Topics covered include Confederate troop strength and movements, the military service of slaves in the Confederacy, and reminiscences of officers and battles by various individuals.
Arrangement
Arrangement
The finding aid arranges the items alphabetically within each series. The items are physically located in a bound volume in no particular order. The page numbers in the container listing refer to the page number on which the item appears.
Organization
Organized into the following three series: I. George Washington Campbell Papers, 1793-1833; II. David Hubbard Papers, 1834-1861; III. Richard Stoddert Ewell Papers, 1862-1885.
Contents List
- George Washington Campbell Papers, 1793-1833, 117 items
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Joseph Anderson, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 23 November 1814, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket, additional cover leaf with p.s. on verso
  - William P. Anderson, Federal Bottom, Nashville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 9 January 1809, 7 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - W[illiam] P. Anderson, Craggy Hope, Murfreesboro, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 30 July 1821, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - J[ohn] Armstrong, Baltimore, Maryland, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 4 September 1814, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - J[ohn] A[rmstrong], Baltimore, Maryland, to [James Madison], 4 September 1814, 1 p., MsL (transcript)
  - G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, to General John Armstrong, 2 January 1815, 3 p., ALS (draft) with docket
  - John Jacob Astor, Paris, [France], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 24 July 1819, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket.
  - John Jacob Astor, Rome, [Italy], to [G. W. C.], 3 p., ALS
  - Samuel P. Black, Murfreesboro, [Tennessee], to G. W. C., Nashville, [Tennessee], 31 December 1821, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Robert Brent to G. W. C., at Mrs. Suter's, 15 January 1816, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Robert Brent, Washington, [D. C.], to Robert Sacrey, Nashville, Tennessee, 20 January 1816, 2 p., MsL (copy) with docket in the hand of G. W. C.
  - J[ames] Bright, Fayettesville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 29 November 1821, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - John Brown, Fort Armstrong, Cossa River, to G. W. C., Kingston, Tennessee, forwarded to Washington, [D. C.], 22 November 1813, 4 p., ALS with additional and docket
  - Thomas Brown, Kingston, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 25 December 1813, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - A[nthony] Butler, Russellville, Kentucky, to G. W. C., Washington, D. C., 3 February 1809, 5 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - An[thony] Butler, Russellville, Kentucky, to G. W. C., Knoxville, Tennessee, 15 September 1808, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - John W. Campbell, Knoxville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 5 November 1811, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - John W. Campbell, Knoxville, [Tennessee], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 20 August 1815, 4 p., ALS with additional and docket
  - Samuel Carswell, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 7 September 1814, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - George Coalter, Fayetteville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 2 July 1814, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - John Cocke, Rutledge, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 24 December [1805], 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - John Cocke, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 18 January 1822, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - William H. Crawford, Paris, France, to [G. W. C.], 20 April 1814, 4 p., ALS
  - William H. Crawford, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., 16 May 1820, 3 p., ALS
  - H[enry A. S.] Dearborn, Boston, Massachusetts, to G. W. C., 6 January 1819, 2 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - H[enry] A. S. Dearborn, Boston, [Massachusetts], to G. W. C., Tennessee, 12 January 1822, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - H[enry] A. S. Dearborn, Boston, [Massachusetts], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 11 April 1822, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - John Dickinson, Franklin, [Tennessee], to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 4 May 1814, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - J[ohn] H[enry] Eaton, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 29 January 1822, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - J. Edgar, Kaskaskia, Illinois, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 19 November 1821, 1 p., ALS with additional page and docket. On verso is 1 page, autographed letter, draft reply, from [G. W. C.], Nashville, Tennessee, to [J. Edgar], 1 January 1822.
  - A. H. Everett, Bruselles, [Kingdom of the Netherlands], to G. W. C., Russia, 7 January 1819, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf
  - George W. Ewing, Madrid, [Spain], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 2 March 1819, 4 p., ALS
  - Edmund P. Gaines, Fort Stoddert, Mississippi Territory, to G. W. C., Washington, D. C., forwarded to Nashville, Tennessee, 22 April 1809, 4 p., ALS, with 3 p. enclosure (petition) with additional page and docket
  - Edmund P. Gaines, Fort Stoddert, Missouri Territory, to G. W. C., Knoxville, forwarded to Nashville, Tennessee, 22 May 1809, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Albert Gallatin, Paris, [France], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 18 August 1819, 8 p., ALS
  - Albert Gallatin, Paris, [France], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 15 September 1819, 6 p., ALS
  - John Lowry, John Walker, Ridge, Richard Taylor, Chew, Washington, [D. C.], to George Graham, Dept. of War, 22 March 1816, 1 p., MsL (copy) with cover leaf and docket in the hand of G. W. C.
  - [G. W. C.], Washington, [D. C.], to George Graham, Acting Secretary of War, 11 January 1817, 5 p., AL (draft) with docket
  - George Graham to Andrew Jackson, 13 January 1817, 2 p., MsL (copy) with docket in the hand of G. W. C.
  - George Graham, Dept. of War, to G. W. C., Senate of the U. S., 18 January 1817, 1 p., MsLS and docket with enclosure
  - Peter Hagner, Dept. of War, to G. W. C., U. S. Senate, 8 January 1817, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - Alexander Hamilton, Philadelphia, to John Armstrong, Jr., 1 April 1793, 2 p., MsL (copy) with manuscript notes on cover leaf
  - Levet Harris, Burlington, New Jersey, to G. W. C., Boston, [Massachusetts], 7 July 1818, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - David Hubbard, Florence, Alabama, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 2 December 1821, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - David Hubbard, Florence, [Alabama], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 12 December 1821, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - D[avid] Hubbard, Courtland, [Alabama], to [G. W. C.], 9 May 1833, 2 p., ALS
  - Andrew Jackson, Captain Craigs, to George W. Campbell, Knoxville, [Tennessee], 13 April 1804, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf
  - Andrew Jackson, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Knoxville, [Tennessee], 28 April 1804, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf
  - Andrew Jackson, Hermitage, to G. W. C., Knoxville, Tennessee, 5 August 1805, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Andrew Jackson, Nashville, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 15 January 1807, 5 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - [G. W. C.], 3 April 1828, 1 p., AN (draft); Regarding 15 January 1807 letter from Andrew Jackson to George Washington Campbell
  - Andrew Jackson to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 5 August 1811, 1 p., ALS with p.s. and additional leaf
  - Andrew Jackson, Hermitage, [Tennessee], to G. W. C., Nashville, 14 February 1828, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Andrew Jackson to Mrs. Mary Polk, care of Mr. Lucius Polk, Spring Hill, near Columbia, Tennessee, 26 November 1832, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf
  - Thomas Jefferson, Monticello, to G. W. C., Washington, D. C., 8 May 1814, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - G. W. C., Nashville, [Tennessee], to Thomas Jefferson, 9 September 1815, 3 p., ALS with docket (draft)
  - Thomas Jefferson, Monticello, Virginia, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, forwarded to Washington, [D. C.], 15 October 1815, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Richard M. Johnson, W[ashington, D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennesse, 29 October 1814, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf, p.s. and docket
  - G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, to Richard M. Johnson, 27 November 1814, 16 p., ALS (draft) with docket
  - W[illiam] Jones, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], to G. W. C., 7 November 1820, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - John D. Lewis, St. Petersburg, [Russia], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 27 May 1821, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - J[ohn] D. L[ewis], St. Petersburg, [Russia], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 21 July 1821, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - Thomas McCorry, Knoxville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 21 December 1814, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Thomas McCorry, Knoxville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 7 January 1815, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Thomas McCorry, Knoxville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 4 February 1815, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - T[homas] Macdonough, U. S. S. Guerriere, Cronstadt and [Russia], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 27 September 1818, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - James Madison, Montpelier, to G. W. C., 7 May 1814, 2 p., ALS
  - James Madison, Montpelier, to [G. W. C.], 25 May 1814, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - [G. W. C.], Washington, D. C., to [James Madison], 26 September 1814, 2 p., AL (draft) with cover leaf and docket
  - James Madison to G. W. C., 27 September 1814, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - James Madison, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., 2 November 1814, 2 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - [G. W. C.], Nashville, Tennessee, to [James Madison], 15 December 1814, 3 p., AL (draft) with docket
  - [G. W. C.], Nashville, Tennessee, to James Madison, 15 December 1814, 3 p., AL (draft)
  - Josiah Meigs, General Land Office, [Washington, D. C.], to G. W. C., 7 January 1822, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - Samuel Mitchell, New York, [New York], to G. W. C., 13 May 1818, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Samuel Mitchell, New York, [New York], to G. W. C., Boston, [Massachusetts], 22 June 1818, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - James Monroe, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 16 October 1813, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - James Monroe, Sweet Springs, Virginia, to [G. W. C.], 6 September 1815, 2 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - James Monroe, Washington, [D. C.], to [G. W. C.], 11 April 1818, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf
  - James Monroe, Oak Hill, [Virginia], to [G. W. C.], 11 April 1828, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - Thomas Munroe, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 11 February 1822, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - "The Memorialists" [John Nancarrow, et. al.], New Orleans, to G. W. C., Washington, D. C., 7 February 1809, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket and MsN laid in, enclosure
  - Petition, John Nancarrow, Alexander Fulton, Josiah S. Johnston, John Hughes, David B. Morgan to U. S. Congress, [7 February 1809], 2 p., printed document; Enclosed in the "The Memorialists" to George Washington Campbell, 7 February 1809
  - [G. W. C.], Nashville, Tennessee, to John Norvell, Washington, [D. C.], 19 January 1815, 4 p., ALS (draft) with docket
  - J. Norvell, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 10 February 1815, 4 p., ALS with additional and docket
  - John Norvell, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 3 March 1815, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Josiah Nichol, Nashville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 4 January 1823, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Usher Parsons, U. S. Frigate Guerriere, to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, Russia, 8 October 1818, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - William Pinkney, Baltimore, [Maryland], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 29 July 1818, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - William Pinkney, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 19 January 1821, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - Thomas Plater, Georgetown, D. C., to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 27 January 1815, 2 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - A[lexander] Robertson, New York, [New York], to G. W. C., St. Petersburgh, [Russia], 18 July 1819, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf
  - Richard Rush, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., 2 November 1814, 4 p., ALS with docket
  - Richard Rush, Washington, D. C., to G. W. C., 22 April 1815, 2 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - G. W. C., Nashville, [Tennessee], to Richard Rush, 20 July 1815, 2 p., ALS (draft) with docket
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., 30 November 1818, 2 p., ALS with cover leaf and docket
  - Julian Whiteside, Gallatin, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 21 December 1807, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 2 February 1819, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 1 May 1819, 4 p., ALS with docket
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., 24 July 1819, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., St. Petersburg, [Russia], 25 January 1820, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., 28 February 1820, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - Richard Rush, London, [England], to G. W. C., St., 14 December 1820, 3 p., ALS
  - Jonathan Russell, Stockholm, [Sweden], to G. W. C., 13 September 1818, 3 p., ALS
  - Jonathan Russell, Stockholm, [Sweden], to G. W. C., 19 October 1818, 1 p., ALS with cover leaf
  - Thomas Sumter, Stateburgh, [South Carolina], to [G. W. C.], 11 July 1808, 2 p., ALS
  - James Trimble, Gallatin, [Tennessee], to G. W. C., Knoxville, Tennessee, 19 November 1810, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - M[artin] Van Buren, W[ashington, D. C.], to Miss Mary Easton, Nashville, Tennessee, 4 July 1830, 1 p., ALS [lacking pages] with additional leaf
  - J. B. Varnum, Washington, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Knoxville, Tennessee, 19 March 1810, 5 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - John Vaughn, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], to William Vaughn, London, England, 7 July 1818, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and manuscript note on verso, 18 June 1856
  - John and Benjamin Welles, Boston, [Massachusetts], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 13 April 1822, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - William Whann, Georgetown, [D. C.], to G. W. C., Nashville, Tennessee, 17 February 1875, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - J[enkin] Whiteside, F[elix] Grundy, Thomas Washington, Nashville, [Tennessee], to G. W. C., 12 January 1821, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - [G. W. C.], Nashville, [Tennessee], to Jenkin Whiteside, Felix Grundy, Thomas Washington, Nashville, [Tennessee], 12 January 1821, 2 p., ALS (draft) with cover leaf and docket
  - Jenkin Whiteside, Nashville, Tennessee, to G. W. C., Washington, [D. C.], 4 June 1812, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
- David Hubbard Papers, 1834-1861, 17 items
  - J. J. Abert, Washington, [D. C.], to Major David Hubbard, 22 November 1834, 7 p., ALS
  - J[ohn] C. Calhoun, Washington, [D. C.], to David Hubbard, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], 15 June 1834, 4 p., ALS with additional wrapper
  - J[ohn] C. Calhoun, Washington, [D. C.], to David Hubbard, 12 March 1834, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - J[ohn] C. Calhoun, Senate Chamber, [Washington, D. C.], to David Hubbard, 28 November 1843, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - J[ohn] C. Calhoun, Washington, [D. C.], to D[avid] Hubbard, 22 September 1844, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - C[lement] C[omer] Clay, Washington, [D. C.], to Major David Hubbard, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], 5 July 1838, 1 p., ALS with additional leaf
  - C[lement] C[omer] Clay, Huntsville, [Alabama], to David Hubbard, Kinlock, Alabama, 8 July [18]59, 4 p., ALS
  - Richard N. Cralle, Washington, [D. C.], to David Hubbard, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], 27 April 1838, 3 p., ALS with additional page and docket
  - William R. King, New York, [New York], to David Hubbard, Washington, D. C., 14 May 1844, 6 p., ALS with additional leaf and docket
  - D. H. Lewis, House of Representatives, [Washington, D. C.], to David Hubbard, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], 12 April 1838, 3 p., ALS with additional page
  - D. H. Lewis, House of Representatives, [Washington, D. C.], to David Hubbard, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], 14 April 1838, p., ALS with additional page
  - [D. H. Lewis], House of Representatives, [Washington, D. C.], to [David Hubbard], 28 April 1838, 4 p., AL (portion lacking)
  - James K. Polk, Nashville, [Tennessee], to David Hubbard, Washington, [D. C.], 30 December 1839, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - James K. Polk, Nashville, [Tennessee], to David Hubbard, Washington, [D. C.], 6 April 1840, 4 p., ALS with additional wrapper and docket
  - R[obert] Toombs, Montgomery, Alabama, to R. W. Johnson, Little Rock, Arkansas, 14 May 1861, 1 p., ALS with envelope
  - Henry A. Wise, Richmond, Virginia, to David Hubbard, 3 March 1859, 4 p., ALS
  - Henry A. Wise, Richmond, Virginia, to David Hubbard, 20 March 1859, 6 p., ALS with cover leaf
- Richard Stoddert Ewell Papers, 1862-1885, 16 items
  - [P]. G. T. Beauregard, Charleston, South Carolina, to R. S. Ewell, Gordonsville, Virginia, 24 February 1864, 1 p., ALS
  - Jefferson Davis, Beauvoir, Mississippi, to Major Campbell Brown, Spring Hill, Maury County, Tennessee, 13 August 1885, 3 p., ALS docketed with envelope docketed
  - Jefferson Davis, Beauvoir, Mississippi, to Major Campbell Brown, 14 June 1886, 6 p., ALS
  - U[lysses] S. Grant to James Y. Yeatman, President Western Sanitary Commission, 7 April 1863, 3 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - Isham G. Harris, Dalton, Georgia, to Mrs. General Ewell, 7 March 1864, 10 p., ALS with docket
  - R[obert] E. Lee, Head Quarters, Orange C. H., Virginia, to R. S. Ewell, 11 August 1863, 2 p., ALS with docket
  - R. E. Lee, Headquarters, 18 February 18[64], 1 p., ALS with docket on verso
  - R. E. Lee, Headquarters, to Genl. [R. S. Ewell], 10 May 1864, 2 p., ALS
  - T. J. Jackson to R. S. Ewell, [August 1862], 1 p., ALS with typed note (2 copies)
  - Bradley T. Johnson, Baltimore, [Maryland], to Major Campbell Brown, Nashville, Tennessee, 29 April 1885, 3 p., ALS
  - Preston Johnson, Account of torture in Fort Delaware prison camp, 26 April 1865, 1 p., MsSw with manuscript notes on verso
  - J[oseph] E. Johnston, Columbia, South Carolina, to "My Dear Colonel," 23 January 1865, 2 p., ALS
  - "Map of the Battle Ground of Manassas... by an Officer of Genl. Beauregard's Staff.. July 21, 1861." John Henry pub., P. S. Duval & Son, Philadelphia, Lithographers, 1862, 1 p., printed map; signed "Joseph Horner 1862" in top margin.
  - Charles Marshall to R. S. Ewell, 27 March 1865, 2 p., ALS
  - Charles Marshall to R. S. Ewell, 30 March 1865, 2 p., ALS
  - Unknown, Memorandum on Union Military Units, n.d., 2 p., Ms